<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 14:42:26 -0800</pubDate><title><![CDATA[About]]></title><url><![CDATA[about]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[About]]></menu><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;section&gt; &lt;article&gt;&lt;p&gt;For over 64 years, these four elements laid the foundation for lifelong scholarship and citizenship for the students at Tucker-Maxon School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1947 by a Harvard trained attorney whose daughter was deaf, Paul Boley wished his daughter to have the gifts of speech and laughter. From the earliest beginnings with classes held in his dining room to becoming a private boarding school during the 1950&#039;s to the current model where students - deaf and hearing - share the importance of listing and spoken language for a lifetime of learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This nationally acclaimed school attracts students whose famillies have relocated from all over the United States, as well as internationally, in order to provide their children with The Tucker-Maxon School experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt; &lt;article&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;OUR MISSION&lt;/em&gt; is to have deaf and hearing children talking, learning, and achieving excellence together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;OUR VISION&lt;/em&gt; is for The Tucker-Maxon Oral School to be a parent&#039;s first choice for listening and spoken language instruction, delivering services of outstanding quality to students, birth through grade 5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt; &lt;/section&gt; ]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[admin]]></author><hero><![CDATA[http://tmos.benjaminjfisher.com/data/uploads/images/gazebo.gif]]></hero><hero><![CDATA[http://tmos.benjaminjfisher.com/data/uploads/images/gazebo.gif]]></hero><creDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 14:42:26 -0800</creDate><user><![CDATA[admin]]></user><menuOrder><![CDATA[6]]></menuOrder></item>
