<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 17:46:21 -0800</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Admissions]]></title><url><![CDATA[admissions]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Admissions]]></menu><menuStatus><![CDATA[Y]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;section&gt; &lt;article&gt;&lt;h4 id=&quot;hearing&quot;&gt;Hearing&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first step is for you and your child to visit our campus and meet with our staff. You can get basic information by looking through our website and talking to us on the phone, but nothing replaces a visit to be able to understand who we are and what we do here at Tucker-Maxon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next step is to submit an Intent To Enroll form along with a non-refundable $75.00 registration fee. Your payment will be refunded if admission is not offered. Academic and/or medical records will be requested as needed. After review of your application and determine acceptance within a short time, you will receive a letter of acceptance. Please note that we need to meet your child and receive your Intent to Enroll form before we can offer admission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your letter of acceptance will outline the amount and due date for payment of the first month&rsquo;s tuition. Payment of the initial tuition will confirm your enrollment. For families applying mid-year, the pro-rated first month&#039;s tuition secures your child&rsquo;s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In August, a registration packet will be mailed to you with information on classroom assignments and details on the upcoming year. Complete registration paperwork and return it to the school office. We need to have a completed Health, Emergency and Authorization form and immunization records before your child may attend class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt; &lt;article&gt;&lt;h4 id=&quot;hearing-impaired&quot;&gt;Hearing Impaired&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first step is for you and your child to visit our campus and meet with our staff. We may ask that your child have speech, listening and /or audiological evaluations at this time from our staff audiologist and speech pathologist. We will also need the following information available at the time of your visit:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most recent audiogram&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most recent IEP or IFSP&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior to admission, we will need to review additional information which may include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Audiology report&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Speech/language evaluations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A statement of eligibility for special education from your school district, if you have one&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Any other pertinent school or medical records&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After review, our admissions team will decide whether Tucker-Maxon is an appropriate placement for your child and we will notify you of our decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next step is to submit an Intent to Enroll form along with a non-refundable $75 registration fee. This fee may be waived if it presents a hardship. We are able to offer significant financial assistance to most of our families based on demonstrated need. Completion of a Financial Assistance application is required for documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Financial Assistance Committee will meet within a short time to determine your award. At that time a letter of acceptance will be sent which will outline the amount and due date for payment of the first month&rsquo;s tuition. Payment of the initial tuition will confirm your enrollment. For families applying mid-year, the pro-rated first month&rsquo;s tuition secures your child&rsquo;s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In August, a registration packet will be mailed to you with information on classroom assignments and details on the upcoming year. Complete registration paperwork and return it to the school office. We need to have a completed Health, Emergency and Authorization form and immunization records before your child may attend class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt; &lt;article&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Contact&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;An interested family should setup an appointment with the secretary (503-235-6551) to visit the school and meet with the classroom teachers. After their visit, parents may pay the deposit to hold a place in the class. At that time they will be given enrollment forms to fill out. Generally, classes are finalized in August and families will receive registration packets from us that month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt; &lt;/section&gt; ]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[nate]]></author><hero><![CDATA[http://tmos.benjaminjfisher.com/data/uploads/images/classroom_2.jpg]]></hero><alert><![CDATA[]]></alert><hero><![CDATA[http://tmos.benjaminjfisher.com/data/uploads/images/classroom_2.jpg]]></hero><alert><![CDATA[]]></alert><creDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 17:46:21 -0800</creDate><user><![CDATA[nate]]></user><menuOrder><![CDATA[3]]></menuOrder></item>
