<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<item><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 14:21:19 -0800</pubDate><title><![CDATA[Elementary]]></title><url><![CDATA[elementary]]></url><meta><![CDATA[]]></meta><metad><![CDATA[]]></metad><menu><![CDATA[Elementary]]></menu><menuOrder><![CDATA[0]]></menuOrder><menuStatus><![CDATA[]]></menuStatus><template><![CDATA[template.php]]></template><parent><![CDATA[programs]]></parent><content><![CDATA[&lt;section&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Tucker-Maxon Elementary&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Laying the Foundation for Lifelong Scholarship and Citizenship&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h5&gt;The Tucker Maxon Philosophy&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Tucker-Maxon there is an intentional focus on listening and spoken language. A language-rich environment is created with many opportunities for open-ended discussion, hypothesis, and critical thinking. Vocabulary, abstract language and question comprehension also are critical to a child&#039;s success in school and occupy a prominent place in our curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A unique part of our philosophy is the co-enrollment of typically hearing students and students who are deaf or hard of hearing. Learning alongside students who are deaf or hard of hearing, our hearing students learn to value differences. Learning alongside typically hearing students, our students who are deaf or hard of hearing improve their listening and spoken language skills. Responding to fit your child&#039;s individual needs, small, collaborative groups lay the groundwork for lifelong scholarship and citizenship. Those who need extra help, get it. Those who are ahead of the group in a particular area are able to grow at their own pace. Each student is known and each student is valued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;Children Learning Together &mdash; How it Works&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;A typical class has a majority of children with typical hearing and several children who are deaf or hard of hearing. Each class is taught by a certified teacher. Children with hearing loss receive additional services from a licensed teacher of the deaf or hard of hearing, and on-site speech-language pathology and audiology services. All children receive ample support from classroom teachers and volunteers in individual, small and large group activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All classrooms are equipped with a sound-field system for the benefit of the hearing as well as the children with hearing loss. A sound-field system makes it easier for the students to hear the teacher&rsquo;s voice. Research has found that sound-field systems may improve literacy development in all children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5&gt;The Tucker-Maxon Curriculum&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nationally-recognized curricula in reading and math incorporate Oregon&rsquo;s benchmarks. Singapore Math was recently chosen as the Elementary Math program. For Reading, Tucker-Maxon selected Super Kids by the Rowland Reading Foundation for grades K-2, and Imagine It! by SRA Reading Programs for grades three through five. Social Studies and Science are an important part of our core curriculum as well. A culminating experience for the Elementary students is Cultural Night. On Cultural Night, the Elementary students demonstrate through child-written skits what they learned from their extended study of a country. The selected country is studied by the whole department&mdash;learning about culture, music, art, food, recreational activities, sports, terrain, animals and wildlife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;]]></content><private><![CDATA[]]></private><author><![CDATA[nate]]></author><hero><![CDATA[http://tmos.benjaminjfisher.com/data/uploads/images/birds.gif]]></hero><hero><![CDATA[http://tmos.benjaminjfisher.com/data/uploads/images/birds.gif]]></hero><creDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 14:21:19 -0800</creDate><user><![CDATA[nate]]></user></item>
